mywbut.com 2014-11-21

# mywbut.com | Privacy Policy

**Personal information collected**

We collect information:

  * When you register an account to become a **mywbut.com** user (“User”), such as your name, e-mail, college, stream, year, and a password.
  * When you add to your profile with further information about yourself or your private contacts, Answers and other Member-to-Member communication.
  * We use cookies and other technologies to recognize you, customize your experience, and serve advertisements.
  * Like all websites, we automatically receive from your internet use information like your IP address, the URLs of sites from which you arrive or leave the mywbut.com website, your type of browser, your operating system, your mobile provider, your mobile device, and your ISP.

**Uses of personal information**

We use the information you provide to:

  * Enable you to share your information and communicate with other Users.
  * Administer your account with us and customize the service we provide to you and other Users; and to
  * Send you service or promotional communications through email and notices on the mywbut.com website.

We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personal identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. You are provided with the means to control whether or not you want to fill your contact information. 

**Your obligations to other Users.** ****

  * Do not abuse the **mywbut.com** service by using it to spam, abuse, harass, or otherwise violate the User Agreement or Privacy Policy.

**Security**

  * Personal information you provide will be secured with industry standards and technology. Since the internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to LinkedIn. There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.
  * You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications at all times.

**How to contact us**

  * If you have any questions or comments please email us at [admin@mywbut.com](mailto:admin@mywbut.com)
